undark.org 2017-06-06

# Privacy - Undark

### Privacy Policy

Undark Magazine, a publication of the Knight Science Journalism Program at MIT, is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Undark website and governs data collection and usage. By using the Undark website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

##### Collection of Your Personal Information

Undark may collect personally identifiable information, anonymous demographic information, and information about your computer hardware and software. Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Undark public message boards, such information may be collected and used by others. Undark encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Undark so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Undark is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Undark website.

##### Use/Security of Your Personal Information

For the purposes of an Undark email newsletter or other reader communications, Undark may offer to collect your name and email address.

Undark does not sell, rent or lease its user lists to third parties.

Undark may keep track of the links and pages that users access within the Undark website, in order to determine what Undark content is most popular.

Undark is committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, Undark has put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information Undark collects online.

##### Use of Cookies

As is true of most websites, Undark gathers certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. Undark uses this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyse trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

Undark does not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

Undark may use a third-party tracking service called that uses cookies to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site such as internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp. Undark uses this information to better gain an understanding about how our site is used by visitors, helping us to update and improve the web site.

##### Changes to this Statement

Undark will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy. Undark encourages you to periodically review this Statement of Privacy to be informed of how Undark is using and protecting your information.

##### Contact Information

Undark welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Undark has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Undark at [info@undark.org](mailto:info@undark.org). We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
